The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Five Elements Sect's Zhou Yi ?
Junior Chi Hu of the Giant Demon Clan
greets Senior.
Junior has heard Senior's name since birth.
This little guy was very quick to react.
It seems that
you had already noticed me on your way here.
Junior only had a feeling
but I wasn’t sure.
I have already taken the coffin
1000 years ago.
The three of you
should leave now.
There is indeed a third layer.
The entrance
is this pool of water.
If you're not afraid of death,
you can try going in.
It's so crowded here !
What's your intention
in following me ?
I don’t have any intentions.
I’m just a bit interested
in the third layer.
What ?
will you not let me in ?
I'm afraid these two
are not Soul Formation cultivators.
My life artifact was damaged,
that was a big price.
I can't just return empty-handed.
Brother Ceng,
do you intend to go in,
or will you leave ?
These two,
who are they ?
I don't know who the second one is,
maybe he's related to the Corpse Sect.
But this one is Zhou Yi,
he's one of the few Soul Transformation old monsters of planet Suzaku.
This guy
has a very strange nickname:
Corpse Lover.
Corpse Lover ?!
Don’t say it out loud
or he will kill you !
I’m going down to see.
How about we go together ?
If the two Soul Transformation deal with each other,
we might be able
to explore the third layer.
Third layer of the\Noverlapping fragments\NRain Celestial Realm
Red Butterfly's\NSpirit Gathering Gourd
Chi Hu's\NSpirit Gathering Pouch
The celestial spiritual energy here is very dense.
It must be because of those crystals.
What are they ?
Even with my cultivation,
I can't move them at all.
Old man,
don’t push me too far !
There is a lot of celestial spiritual energy here.
Why are you still following me ?
You have the scent of death.
Of course I need to follow you.
Scram !
Imperial Spirit Law ?
You're Zhou Yi !
I have heard about you.
I was wondering why
you had such a powerful scent of death.
If the two of us fight here,
this fragment will collapse.
You think you can escape
but let me tell you this.
There is a total of 6 fragments overlapping.
One collapses, they all collapse.
You must be the Corpse Sect’s Head Elder.
Even an Ascendant cultivator
wouldn't be able to escape.
Are you sure
we fight ?
If these two fight for real,
then the fragment will collapse for sure.
Little girl,
I’m going to borrow your body for a bit.
Senior,
do you know this object ?
The symbol of the core disciples of Suzaku,
the Open Peace Bracelet.
This bracelet is linked to my soul.
If I were to die,
it will explode and destroy this fragment.
Even if you escape,
Suzaku will hunt you down.
You would have no place to live.
Little girl,
relax.
I won't kill you.
Zhou Yi,
I’m going to borrow this girl’s body to fight you.
That way,
we won't destroy the fragment.
You should go choose someone as well.
Why should I fight you ?
Old man,
what exactly do you want ?
You have the corpse of a celestial on you.
My nose can’t be wrong.
I want that body !
You...
want to steal Ting'er !
Those who also want Ting'er
must die !
You, come here.
Become my avatar.
Not only will you not die,
but you will be able to experience my domain.
Among the 3 little fellows,
I chose the one with a five-element body
and you chose the one from the Giant Demon Clan.
The only one left is a useless normal person.
Scram !
Senior,
kill him.
If you kill him,
I’ll give up on resisting
and will fully support you !
if you wish for this place to collapse,
you can try !
A Restriction Flag ?
He isn't lying.
Once he places that last restriction
it will trigger a tribulation.
In the Celestial Realm,
this kind of Divine Retribution
will kill everyone.
Since I’m already here,
then I’m in no rush to leave.
Let's watch how Soul Transformation cultivators fight.
Zhou Yi's\NOrigin Soul
The Origin Soul
can possess Soul Formation cultivators ?
That's a Soul Transformation level technique.
Sun Tai's\NBlack Dragon Origin Soul
They suppressed their cultivation to peak Soul Formation
to avoid a fragment collapse.
My domain
is craze.
Because I have gone crazy for love,
I have reached the epitome of madness.
This obsession
can shake the heavens and the earth !
I will use your body
and let you feel
the domain I haven't shown in 1000 years.
Obsession isn't always for a person.
It can be for an object.
Your obsession
is this axe.
Your Dao Heart
is also this axe.
As long as it's intact,
your will to fight will persist !
Fight !
Chi Hu is only at Soul Formation
but this fighting aura feels like it could slay Celestials.
Zhou Yi’s domain
is indeed strange.
So that's his Craze Domain.
How could she be missing an earth spirit ?
Fight !
Accept your death !
Zhou Yi,
that's enough !
I am the Corpse Sect’s Head Elder,
it doesn't matter if your domain is strong.
With that Junior's Soul Formation body
can you destroy my Origin Soul ?
Fight !
With his fighting spirit,
Soul Transformation
can be defeated.
His Origin Soul
has been destroyed.
Sun Tai is dead.
With his Dao Heart,
he could slay Celestials.
What an incredible domain.
My Dao Heart...
what is it ?
No !!!
I won't allow anyone to steal my Ting'er !
Zhou Yi,
your domain is exceptional.
You managed to kill one of my Origin Souls.
But as the Corpse Sect’s Head Elder,
Sun Tai's\NOrigin Soul
did you think I only had one Origin Soul ?
Give Ting'er
back to me !
Ting'er ?
Zhou Yi,
you even gave the corpse a name.
1000 years ago
Five Elements Sect
Tang Xiong\NFive Elements Sect\NLate stage Soul Transformation
You made a mistake !
You were the next sect leader...
But you stole celestial jades
that belonged to the sect
just for a woman !
A dead woman !
Traitor !
You... you...
That's right, he is Zhou Yi.
He's a crazy disgusting corpse lover.
This is the corpse of a Celestial.
I’m afraid that when she was born,
you were still in the reincarnation cycle.
Give Ting'er
back to me !!!
No !
Ting'er...
They don't understand your beauty.
Don't worry.
I will always be with you,
forever.
Incredible...
This Celestial's corpse seems to have
a powerful attraction force.
How dangerous.
Good.
Good !
When she was alive,
she must have had a high status in the Celestial Realm.
Zhou Yi,
I’m using the Corpse Sect’s treasure
which is made for sealing Origin Souls.
Now,
this corpse will definitely be mine !
I advise you
to return to your body.
Unless you want to die in the Celestial Realm.
You are a madman !
Give Ting'er
BACK TO ME !!!
Are you really burning your Origin Soul
just for a corpse ?
You...
You're a madman !
Madman !
If you are willing to die for a corpse,
I won't accompany you.
Ting'er,
no one can take you away,
no one…
I am out of spiritual energy and artifacts.
I have to get out as soon as possible.
This woman has tried to kill me 3 times.
If I don't deal with her now,
she'll be a problem in the future.
Ceng Niu,
what are you doing !?
I'm killing you.
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.